flvpro.com 2012-06-11

# FLV Pro

**Version 1.0 (February 2, 2009)**

## Website Privacy Policy

This Website Privacy Policy (this "Policy") applies with respect to the information that we collect from the Design and Marketing DM S.A. (the "Company") Website, located at www.loudmo.com , and explains how we collect, use and disclose your personal information in connection with our services. Amendments to this Policy will be posted at this URL. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof. While the Company may update you of any changes to its Privacy Policy, it is your obligation to review the terms of this Privacy Policy and stay current therewith.

**I. INFORMATION COLLECTED**

We collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities through your IP address, computer settings or most-recently visited URL. Personally identifiable information is personal information about you including your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, and that which is not otherwise publicly available. We may also ask you to provide certain non-personally identifiable information about yourself, such as your age, household income, buying preferences, etc. Personally identifiable information about you is collected when you voluntarily submit such information to us, by, for example, filling out a survey or registration form. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other Company services or third parties to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.

**II. USE OF INFORMATION**

In general, we will only use the information you provide to us for purposes we deem appropriate. We may use your information (ourselves or utilizing third-party companies) to deliver you information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners and affiliates, trend analysis, pattern detection, and site administration. Your information may also be used to contact you when necessary and may be shared with or sold to other companies that may want to contact you with offers that we (or they) believe are consistent with your preferences. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings from Company and other entities by following the instructions set forth in the opt-out section below.

Non-personal demographic and profile data is used to tailor your experience at our site, showing you content we think you might be interested in. This information may also be shared with advertisers on an aggregate non-personal basis. We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

The Company may also disclose your information upon a transfer or sale to another entity of the Company or upon any other corporate reorganization.

**III. USE OF IP ADDRESSES**

We use your IP Address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website.

**IV. USE OF COOKIES**

Cookies are an industry standard used by most major Websites. When you view our Website we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard drive and steal information. Rather, they help you navigate a Website as easily as possible. We use cookies to improve the quality of our services, deliver content specific to your interests and to prevent you from reentering all your registration data at each connection.

We may use an outside advertisement server company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Through banner ads the advertisement server company may set and access their cookies on your computer. We do not have access to information that would confirm the use of cookies by the advertisement server company. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policy, not this one. You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features may not function properly as a result.

**V. SECURITY**

Our site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "absolute security" on the Internet, we make good faith efforts to take every step to ensure the safety of your personal information, whenever reasonably possible.

**VI. OTHER WEBSITES; LINKS**

Our Website contains links to other Websites. Because this Policy only applies to the Company Website itself and not linked Websites, you should examine the privacy policy of any other Websites that you access from the Company Website. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other Websites.

**VII. CORRECT; UPDATE**

The Company allows its users the option to change or modify information previously provided. This may be done through the following methods:

(1) E-mail the information to update@loudmo.com   
(2) Visit the Customer Service section of the site and follow the appropriate instructions.

Unfortunately, to the extent that such information is also stored in other databases, we cannot always ensure that such corrections or deletions will reach the other databases. We will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is removed from or corrected in our records.

**VIII. CHOICE; OPT OUT**

You may opt-out of receiving communications from our partners, and from us, by the following means:

(1) Send an e-mail to update@loudmo.com   
(2) Visit the Customer Service section of the site and follow the appropriate instructions.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Company service, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them absent a cancellation of services with the Company.

**IX. PUBLIC FORUMS**

This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Contacting us:

If you have any questions about this Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you can contact us at privacy@loudmo.com.
